A Guide to the Militia Commission Papers, 1777-1858
Library of Virginia
- Series II. Militia Commissions, 1777-1858., Extent: 66.71 cu. ft. (169 boxes). (Box 3-171)
  - Subseries A. Counties, 1777-1858.
    - Fairfax County, 1826. (Box 43, Folder 36)
    - Fairfax County, 1827. (Box 43, Folder 37)
    - Fairfax County, 1829. (Box 43, Folder 38)
    - Fairfax County, 1830. (Box 43, Folder 39)
    - Fairfax County, 1831. (Box 43, Folder 40)
    - Fairfax County, 1832. (Box 43, Folder 41)
    - Fairfax County, 1833. (Box 43, Folder 42)
    - Fairfax County, 1834. (Box 43, Folder 43)
    - Fairfax County, 1835. (Box 43, Folder 44)
    - Fairfax County, 1836. (Box 43, Folder 45)
    - Fairfax County, 1837. (Box 43, Folder 46)
    - Fairfax County, 1838. (Box 43, Folder 47)
    - Fairfax County, 1839. (Box 43, Folder 48)
    - Fairfax County, 1840. (Box 43, Folder 49)
    - Fairfax County, 1841. (Box 43, Folder 50)
    - Fairfax County, 1842. (Box 43, Folder 51)
    - Fairfax County, 1843. (Box 43, Folder 52)
    - Fairfax County, 1844. (Box 43, Folder 53)
    - Fairfax County, 1845. (Box 43, Folder 54)
    - Fairfax County, 1846. (Box 43, Folder 55)
    - Fairfax County, 1847. (Box 43, Folder 56)
    - Fairfax County, 1848. (Box 43, Folder 57)
    - Fairfax County, 1849. (Box 43, Folder 58)
    - Fairfax County, 1851. (Box 43, Folder 59)
    - Fairfax County, 1852. (Box 43, Folder 60)
    - Fairfax County, undated. (Box 43, Folder 61)
    - Fauquier County, 1784. (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Fauquier County, 1785. (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Fauquier County, 1787. (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Fauquier County, 1788. (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Fauquier County, 1789. (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Fauquier County, 1793. (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Fauquier County, 1794. (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Fauquier County, 1795. (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Fauquier County, 1796. (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Fauquier County, 1797. (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Fauquier County, 1798. (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Fauquier County, 1799. (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Fauquier County, 1800. (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Fauquier County, 1801. (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Fauquier County, 1802. (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Fauquier County, 1803. (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Fauquier County, 1804. (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Fauquier County, 1805. (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Fauquier County, 1806. (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - Fauquier County, 1807. (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Fauquier County, 1808. (Box 44, Folder 21)
    - Fauquier County, 1809. (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - Fauquier County, 1810. (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - Fauquier County, 1811. (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - Fauquier County, 1812. (Box 44, Folder 25)
    - Fauquier County, 1813. (Box 44, Folder 26)
    - Fauquier County, 1814. (Box 44, Folder 27)
    - Fauquier County, 1815. (Box 44, Folder 28)
    - Fauquier County, 1816. (Box 44, Folder 29)
    - Fauquier County, 1817. (Box 44, Folder 30)
    - Fauquier County, 1818. (Box 44, Folder 31)
    - Fauquier County, 1819. (Box 44, Folder 32)
    - Fauquier County, 1820. (Box 44, Folder 33)
    - Fauquier County, 1821. (Box 44, Folder 34)
    - Fauquier County, 1822. (Box 44, Folder 35)
    - Fauquier County, 1823. (Box 44, Folder 36)
    - Fauquier County, 1824. (Box 44, Folder 37)
    - Fauquier County, 1825. (Box 44, Folder 38)
    - Fauquier County, 1826. (Box 44, Folder 39)
    - Fauquier County, 1827. (Box 44, Folder 40)
    - Fauquier County, 1828. (Box 44, Folder 41)
    - Fauquier County, 1829. (Box 44, Folder 42)
    - Fauquier County, 1830. (Box 44, Folder 43)
    - Fauquier County, 1831. (Box 44, Folder 44)
    - Fauquier County, 1832. (Box 44, Folder 45)
    - Fauquier County, 1833. (Box 44, Folder 46)
    - Fauquier County, 1834. (Box 44, Folder 47)
    - Fauquier County, 1835. (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Fauquier County, 1836. (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Fauquier County, 1837. (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Fauquier County, 1838. (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Fauquier County, 1839. (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Fauquier County, 1840. (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Fauquier County, 1841. (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Fauquier County, 1842. (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Fauquier County, 1843. (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Fauquier County, 1844. (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Fauquier County, 1845. (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Fauquier County, 1846. (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Fauquier County, 1847. (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Fauquier County, 1848. (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Fauquier County, 1849. (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Fauquier County, 1850. (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Fauquier County, 1851. (Box 45, Folder 17)
    - Fauquier County, 1852. (Box 45, Folder 18)
    - Fauquier County, 1853. (Box 45, Folder 19)
    - Fauquier County, undated. (Box 45, Folder 20)
    - Fayette County, 1780. (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Fayette County, 1783. (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Fayette County, 1784. (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Fayette County, 1785. (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Fayette County, 1786. (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Fayette County, 1787. (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Fayette County, 1788. (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Fayette County, 1789. (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Fayette County, 1790. (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Fayette County, 1791. (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Fayette County, 1832. (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Fayette County, 1833. (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Fayette County, 1834. (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Fayette County, 1835. (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Fayette County, 1836. (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Fayette County, 1837. (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Fayette County, 1838. (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Fayette County, 1839. (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Fayette County, 1840. (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Fayette County, 1841. (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - Fayette County, 1842. (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - Fayette County, 1846. (Box 46, Folder 22)
    - Fayette County, 1847. (Box 46, Folder 23)
    - Fayette County, 1848. (Box 46, Folder 24)
    - Fayette County, 1849. (Box 46, Folder 25)
    - Fayette County, 1850. (Box 46, Folder 26)
    - Fayette County, 1851. (Box 46, Folder 27)
    - Fayette County, 1852. (Box 46, Folder 28)
    - Floyd County, 1831. (Box 46, Folder 29)
    - Floyd County, 1833. (Box 46, Folder 30)
    - Floyd County, 1834. (Box 46, Folder 31)
    - Floyd County, 1835. (Box 46, Folder 32)
    - Floyd County, 1836. (Box 46, Folder 33)
    - Floyd County, 1837. (Box 46, Folder 34)
    - Floyd County, 1838. (Box 46, Folder 35)
    - Floyd County, 1839. (Box 46, Folder 36)
    - Floyd County, 1840. (Box 46, Folder 37)
    - Floyd County, 1841. (Box 46, Folder 38)
    - Floyd County, 1842. (Box 46, Folder 39)
    - Floyd County, 1843. (Box 46, Folder 40)
    - Floyd County, 1844. (Box 46, Folder 41)
    - Floyd County, 1845. (Box 46, Folder 42)
    - Floyd County, 1846. (Box 46, Folder 43)
    - Floyd County, 1847. (Box 46, Folder 44)
    - Floyd County, 1848. (Box 46, Folder 45)
    - Floyd County, 1849. (Box 46, Folder 46)
    - Floyd County, 1850. (Box 46, Folder 47)
    - Floyd County, 1851. (Box 46, Folder 48)
    - Floyd County, 1852. (Box 46, Folder 49)
    - Floyd County, 1853. (Box 46, Folder 50)
    - Floyd County, 1854. (Box 46, Folder 51)
    - Fluvanna County, 1783. (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Fluvanna County, 1784. (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Fluvanna County, 1785. (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Fluvanna County, 1786. (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Fluvanna County, 1787. (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Fluvanna County, 1789. (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Fluvanna County, 1790. (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Fluvanna County, 1791. (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Fluvanna County, 1792. (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Fluvanna County, 1793. (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Fluvanna County, 1794. (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Fluvanna County, 1795. (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Fluvanna County, 1796. (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Fluvanna County, 1797. (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Fluvanna County, 1798. (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Fluvanna County, 1799. (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Fluvanna County, 1800. (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Fluvanna County, 1801. (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - Fluvanna County, 1802. (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Fluvanna County, 1803. (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - Fluvanna County, 1804. (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - Fluvanna County, 1805. (Box 47, Folder 22)
    - Fluvanna County, 1806. (Box 47, Folder 23)
    - Fluvanna County, 1807. (Box 47, Folder 24)
    - Fluvanna County, 1808. (Box 47, Folder 25)
    - Fluvanna County, 1809. (Box 47, Folder 26)
    - Fluvanna County, 1810. (Box 47, Folder 27)
    - Fluvanna County, 1811. (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - Fluvanna County, 1812. (Box 47, Folder 29)
    - Fluvanna County, 1813. (Box 47, Folder 30)
    - Fluvanna County, 1814. (Box 47, Folder 31)
    - Fluvanna County, 1815. (Box 47, Folder 32)
    - Fluvanna County, 1816. (Box 47, Folder 33)
    - Fluvanna County, 1817. (Box 47, Folder 34)
    - Fluvanna County, 1818. (Box 47, Folder 35)
    - Fluvanna County, 1819. (Box 47, Folder 36)
    - Fluvanna County, 1820. (Box 47, Folder 37)
    - Fluvanna County, 1821. (Box 47, Folder 38)
    - Fluvanna County, 1822. (Box 47, Folder 39)
    - Fluvanna County, 1823. (Box 47, Folder 40)
    - Fluvanna County, 1824. (Box 47, Folder 41)
    - Fluvanna County, 1825. (Box 47, Folder 42)
    - Fluvanna County, 1826. (Box 47, Folder 43)
    - Fluvanna County, 1827. (Box 47, Folder 44)
    - Fluvanna County, 1828. (Box 47, Folder 45)
    - Fluvanna County, 1829. (Box 47, Folder 46)
    - Fluvanna County, 1830. (Box 47, Folder 47)
    - Fluvanna County, 1831. (Box 47, Folder 48)
    - Fluvanna County, 1832. (Box 47, Folder 49)
    - Fluvanna County, 1833. (Box 47, Folder 50)
    - Fluvanna County, 1834. (Box 47, Folder 51)
    - Fluvanna County, 1835. (Box 47, Folder 52)
    - Fluvanna County, 1836. (Box 47, Folder 53)
    - Fluvanna County, 1837. (Box 47, Folder 54)
    - Fluvanna County, 1838. (Box 47, Folder 55)
    - Fluvanna County, 1839. (Box 47, Folder 56)
    - Fluvanna County, 1840. (Box 47, Folder 57)
    - Fluvanna County, 1841. (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Fluvanna County, 1842. (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Fluvanna County, 1843. (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Fluvanna County, 1844. (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Fluvanna County, 1845. (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Fluvanna County, 1846. (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Fluvanna County, 1847. (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Fluvanna County, 1848. (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Fluvanna County, 1849. (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Fluvanna County, 1850. (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Fluvanna County, 1851. (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Fluvanna County, 1852. (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Fluvanna County, 1853. (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Fluvanna County, undated. (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - Franklin County, 1786. (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Franklin County, 1787. (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Franklin County, 1788. (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Franklin County, 1789. (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Franklin County, 1790. (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Franklin County, 1791. (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Franklin County, 1792. (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Franklin County, 1793. (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Franklin County, 1795. (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Franklin County, 1796. (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Franklin County, 1798. (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Franklin County, 1800. (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Franklin County, 1801. (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Franklin County, 1802. (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Franklin County, 1803. (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Franklin County, 1804. (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Franklin County, 1805. (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - Franklin County, 1806. (Box 49, Folder 18)
    - Franklin County, 1807. (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - Franklin County, 1808. (Box 49, Folder 20)
    - Franklin County, 1809. (Box 49, Folder 21)
    - Franklin County, 1810. (Box 49, Folder 22)
    - Franklin County, 1811. (Box 49, Folder 23)
    - Franklin County, 1812. (Box 49, Folder 24)
    - Franklin County, 1813. (Box 49, Folder 25)
    - Franklin County, 1814. (Box 49, Folder 26)
    - Franklin County, 1815. (Box 49, Folder 27)
    - Franklin County, 1816. (Box 49, Folder 28)
    - Franklin County, 1817. (Box 49, Folder 29)
    - Franklin County, 1818. (Box 49, Folder 30)
    - Franklin County, 1819. (Box 49, Folder 31)
    - Franklin County, 1820. (Box 49, Folder 32)
    - Franklin County, 1821. (Box 49, Folder 33)
    - Franklin County, 1822. (Box 49, Folder 34)
    - Franklin County, 1823. (Box 49, Folder 35)
    - Franklin County, 1824. (Box 49, Folder 36)
    - Franklin County, 1825. (Box 49, Folder 37)
    - Franklin County, 1826. (Box 49, Folder 38)
    - Franklin County, 1827. (Box 49, Folder 39)
    - Franklin County, 1828. (Box 49, Folder 40)
    - Franklin County, 1829. (Box 49, Folder 41)
    - Franklin County, 1830. (Box 49, Folder 42)
    - Franklin County, 1831. (Box 49, Folder 43)
    - Franklin County, 1832. (Box 49, Folder 44)
    - Franklin County, 1833. (Box 49, Folder 45)
    - Franklin County, 1834. (Box 49, Folder 46)
    - Franklin County, 1835. (Box 49, Folder 47)
    - Franklin County, 1836. (Box 49, Folder 48)
    - Franklin County, 1837. (Box 49, Folder 49)
    - Franklin County, 1838. (Box 49, Folder 50)
    - Franklin County, 1839. (Box 49, Folder 51)
    - Franklin County, 1840. (Box 49, Folder 52)
    - Franklin County, 1841. (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Franklin County, 1842. (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Franklin County, 1843. (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Franklin County, 1844. (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Franklin County, 1845. (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Franklin County, 1846. (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Franklin County, 1847. (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Franklin County, 1848. (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Franklin County, 1849. (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Franklin County, 1850. (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Franklin County, 1851. (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Franklin County, 1852. (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Franklin County, 1853. (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Franklin County, 1854. (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Franklin County, 1855. (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Franklin County, 1856. (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Frederick County, 1783. (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Frederick County, 1785. (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Frederick County, 1786. (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Frederick County, 1787. (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Frederick County, 1788. (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Frederick County, 1793. (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - Frederick County, 1794. (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Frederick County, 1795. (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Frederick County, 1796. (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Frederick County, 1797. (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Frederick County, 1798. (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Frederick County, 1799. (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - Frederick County, 1800. (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - Frederick County, 1801. (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - Frederick County, 1802. (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - Frederick County, 1803. (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - Frederick County, 1804. (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - Frederick County, 1805. (Box 51, Folder 18)
    - Frederick County, 1805. (Box 51, Folder 19)
    - Frederick County, 1807. (Box 51, Folder 20)
    - Frederick County, 1808. (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - Frederick County, 1811. (Box 51, Folder 24)
    - Frederick County, 1812. (Box 51, Folder 25)
    - Frederick County, 1813. (Box 51, Folder 26)
    - Frederick County, 1814. (Box 51, Folder 27)
    - Frederick County, 1815. (Box 51, Folder 28)
    - Frederick County, 1816. (Box 51, Folder 29)
    - Frederick County, 1817. (Box 51, Folder 30)
    - Frederick County, 1818. (Box 51, Folder 31)
    - Frederick County, 1819. (Box 51, Folder 32)
    - Frederick County, 1820. (Box 51, Folder 33)
    - Frederick County, 1821. (Box 51, Folder 34)
    - Frederick County, 1822. (Box 51, Folder 35)
    - Frederick County, 1823. (Box 51, Folder 36)
    - Frederick County, 1824. (Box 51, Folder 37)
    - Frederick County, 1825. (Box 51, Folder 38)
    - Frederick County, 1826. (Box 51, Folder 39)
    - Frederick County, 1827. (Box 51, Folder 40)
    - Frederick County, 1828. (Box 51, Folder 41)
    - Frederick County, 1829. (Box 51, Folder 42)
    - Frederick County, 1830. (Box 51, Folder 43)
    - Frederick County, 1831. (Box 51, Folder 44)
    - Frederick County, 1832. (Box 51, Folder 45)
    - Frederick County, 1833. (Box 51, Folder 46)
    - Frederick County, 1834. (Box 51, Folder 47)
    - Frederick County, 1835. (Box 51, Folder 48)
    - Frederick County, 1836. (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - Frederick County, 1837. (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Frederick County, 1838. (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Frederick County, 1839. (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Frederick County, 1840. (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Frederick County, 1841. (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Frederick County, 1842. (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Frederick County, 1843. (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Frederick County, 1844. (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Frederick County, 1845. (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Frederick County, 1846. (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Frederick County, 1847. (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - Frederick County, 1848. (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - Frederick County, 1849. (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Frederick County, 1850. (Box 52, Folder 15)
    - Frederick County, 1851. (Box 52, Folder 16)
    - Frederick County, 1852. (Box 52, Folder 17)
    - Frederick County, 1853. (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - Frederick County, 1855. (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - Frederick County, 1856. (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - Frederick County, undated. (Box 52, Folder 21)
    - Giles County, 1807. (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Giles County, 1808. (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Giles County, 1809. (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Giles County, 1810. (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Giles County, 1811. (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Giles County, 1812. (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Giles County, 1813. (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Giles County, 1814. (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Giles County, 1815. (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Giles County, 1816. (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - Giles County, 1817. (Box 53, Folder 11)
    - Giles County, 1818. (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Giles County, 1819. (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - Giles County, 1820. (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - Giles County, 1821. (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Giles County, 1822. (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Giles County, 1823. (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - Giles County, 1824. (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - Giles County, 1825. (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - Giles County, 1826. (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - Giles County, 1827. (Box 53, Folder 21)
    - Giles County, 1828. (Box 53, Folder 22)
    - Giles County, 1829. (Box 53, Folder 23)
    - Giles County, 1830. (Box 53, Folder 24)
    - Giles County, 1831. (Box 53, Folder 25)
    - Giles County, 1832. (Box 53, Folder 26)
    - Giles County, 1833. (Box 53, Folder 27)
    - Giles County, 1834. (Box 53, Folder 28)
    - Giles County, 1835. (Box 53, Folder 29)
    - Giles County, 1836. (Box 53, Folder 30)
    - Giles County, 1837. (Box 53, Folder 31)
    - Giles County, 1838. (Box 53, Folder 32)
    - Giles County, 1839. (Box 53, Folder 33)
    - Giles County, 1840. (Box 53, Folder 34)
    - Giles County, 1841. (Box 53, Folder 35)
    - Giles County, 1842. (Box 53, Folder 36)
    - Giles County, 1843. (Box 53, Folder 37)
    - Giles County, 1844. (Box 53, Folder 38)
    - Giles County, 1845. (Box 53, Folder 39)
    - Giles County, 1846. (Box 53, Folder 40)
    - Giles County, 1847. (Box 53, Folder 41)
    - Giles County, 1848. (Box 53, Folder 42)
    - Giles County, 1849. (Box 53, Folder 43)
    - Giles County, 1850. (Box 53, Folder 44)
    - Giles County, 1851. (Box 53, Folder 45)
    - Giles County, 1852. (Box 53, Folder 46)
    - Gilmer County, 1845. (Box 53, Folder 47)
    - Gilmer County, 1847. (Box 53, Folder 48)
    - Gilmer County, 1853. (Box 53, Folder 49)
    - Gloucester County, 1783. (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Gloucester County, 1784. (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Gloucester County, 1785. (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - Gloucester County, 1787. (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Gloucester County, 1788. (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Gloucester County, 1789. (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Gloucester County, 1793. (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Gloucester County, 1794. (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Gloucester County, 1795. (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - Gloucester County, 1796. (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - Gloucester County, 1798. (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - Gloucester County, 1799. (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - Gloucester County, 1800. (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - Gloucester County, 1801. (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - Gloucester County, 1802. (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Gloucester County, 1803. (Box 54, Folder 16)
    - Gloucester County, 1804. (Box 54, Folder 17)
    - Gloucester County, 1805. (Box 54, Folder 18)
    - Gloucester County, 1806. (Box 54, Folder 19)
    - Gloucester County, 1807. (Box 54, Folder 20)
    - Gloucester County, 1808. (Box 54, Folder 21)
    - Gloucester County, 1810. (Box 54, Folder 22)
    - Gloucester County, 1811. (Box 54, Folder 23)
    - Gloucester County, 1812. (Box 54, Folder 24)
    - Gloucester County, 1813. (Box 54, Folder 25)
    - Gloucester County, 1814. (Box 54, Folder 26)
    - Gloucester County, 1815. (Box 54, Folder 27)
    - Gloucester County, 1816. (Box 54, Folder 28)
    - Gloucester County, 1817. (Box 54, Folder 29)
    - Gloucester County, 1818. (Box 54, Folder 30)
    - Gloucester County, 1820. (Box 54, Folder 31)
    - Gloucester County, 1821. (Box 54, Folder 32)
    - Gloucester County, 1822. (Box 54, Folder 33)
    - Gloucester County, 1823. (Box 54, Folder 34)
    - Gloucester County, 1824. (Box 54, Folder 35)
    - Gloucester County, 1825. (Box 54, Folder 36)
    - Gloucester County, 1826. (Box 54, Folder 37)
    - Gloucester County, 1827. (Box 54, Folder 38)
    - Gloucester County, 1828. (Box 54, Folder 39)
    - Gloucester County, 1829. (Box 54, Folder 40)
    - Gloucester County, 1830. (Box 54, Folder 41)
    - Gloucester County, 1831. (Box 54, Folder 42)
    - Gloucester County, 1832. (Box 54, Folder 43)
    - Gloucester County, 1833. (Box 54, Folder 44)
    - Gloucester County, 1834. (Box 54, Folder 45)
    - Gloucester County, 1835. (Box 54, Folder 46)
    - Gloucester County, 1836. (Box 54, Folder 47)
    - Gloucester County, 1837. (Box 54, Folder 48)
    - Gloucester County, 1838. (Box 54, Folder 49)
    - Gloucester County, 1839. (Box 54, Folder 50)
    - Gloucester County, 1840. (Box 54, Folder 51)
    - Gloucester County, 1841. (Box 54, Folder 52)
    - Gloucester County, 1842. (Box 54, Folder 53)
    - Gloucester County, 1843. (Box 54, Folder 54)
    - Gloucester County, 1844. (Box 54, Folder 55)
    - Gloucester County, 1845. (Box 54, Folder 56)
    - Gloucester County, 1846. (Box 54, Folder 57)
    - Gloucester County, 1847. (Box 54, Folder 58)
    - Gloucester County, 1848. (Box 54, Folder 59)
    - Gloucester County, 1849. (Box 54, Folder 60)
    - Gloucester County, 1850. (Box 54, Folder 61)
    - Gloucester County, 1851. (Box 54, Folder 62)
    - Gloucester County, 1853. (Box 54, Folder 63)
    - Gloucester County, undated. (Box 54, Folder 64)
    - Goochland County, 1784. (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Goochland County, 1785. (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Goochland County, 1786. (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Goochland County, 1787. (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Goochland County, 1788. (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Goochland County, 1789. (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Goochland County, 1790. (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Goochland County, 1791. (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Goochland County, 1792. (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Goochland County, 1793. (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Goochland County, 1794. (Box 55, Folder 11)
    - Goochland County, 1795. (Box 55, Folder 12)
    - Goochland County, 1796. (Box 55, Folder 13)
    - Goochland County, 1797. (Box 55, Folder 14)
    - Goochland County, 1798. (Box 55, Folder 15)
    - Goochland County, 1799. (Box 55, Folder 16)
    - Goochland County, 1800. (Box 55, Folder 17)
    - Goochland County, 1801. (Box 55, Folder 18)
    - Goochland County, 1802. (Box 55, Folder 19)
    - Goochland County, 1804. (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - Goochland County, 1805. (Box 55, Folder 21)
    - Goochland County, 1806. (Box 55, Folder 22)
    - Goochland County, 1807. (Box 55, Folder 23)
    - Goochland County, 1808. (Box 55, Folder 24)
    - Goochland County, 1809. (Box 55, Folder 25)